(Leonard:)Okay.
The X Tens are online.
(Howard:)Gentlemen, I am now about to send a signal
from this laptop through our local ISP...
...racing down fiber-optic cable
at the speed of light to San Francisco...
(Howard:)...bouncing off a satellite in
geosynchronous orbit to Lisbon, Portugal.
(Howard:)Data packets will be handed off
to submerged transatlantic cables...
...terminating in Halifax, Nova Scotia...
(Howard:)...and transferred across the continent
via microwave relays back to our ISP...
...and the external receiver attached
to this...
(Scene:)...lamp.
(Sheldon:)Look at me, look at me,
I've got goose bumps.
- Are we ready on the stereo?
- Go for stereo.
[MOUSE CLICKS]
[2001: A SPACE ODYSSEY'S "MAIN TITLE"
PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
[LEONARD HUMMING]
[ALL HUMMING]
[ALL IMITATING DRUMS]